<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<CodeList xmlns="urn:fdc:difi.no:2017:vefa:structure:CodeList-1">
    <Title>StatusReasonCode</Title>
    <Identifier>statusReason</Identifier>
    <Version>2021-07-12</Version>
    <Agency>PEPPOL</Agency>
    <Code>
        <Id>BV</Id>
        <Name>Business rule violation, fatal</Name>
        <Description>Error associated with a business rule that indicates a problem that leads to the rejection of the referenced message.</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>BW</Id>
        <Name>Business rule violation, warning</Name>
        <Description>Warning related to a business rule that indicates a problem but that does not hinder further processing at this point in time.</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>SV</Id>
        <Name>Syntax violation</Name>
        <Description>Error associated with a syntax violation that indicates a problem that leads to the rejection of the referenced message.</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>NF</Id>
        <Name>Reference not found</Name>
        <Description>Error caused by a document reference given in the received message that could not be found. Leads to the rejection of the received message.</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>DL</Id>
        <Name>Deadline expired</Name>
        <Description>Error caused by a received message that was not submitted on time. Depending on the procedure availability and elapsed time period, the message may be rejected or conditionally accepted as a result.</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>RF</Id>
        <Name>Request failed</Name>
        <Description>Error caused by a received message that cannot be processed further for technical reasons. Leads to rejection of the received message.</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>WT</Id>
        <Name>Wrong transaction flow</Name>
        <Description>Error caused to a received message that was not sent in the expected sequence of the business process. Leads to the rejection of the received message.</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>IR</Id>
        <Name>Invalid request</Name>
        <Description>Error caused by a received message that cannot be processed further for semantic or business reasons. The message may be rejected or conditionally accepted as a result.</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>MA</Id>
        <Name>Missing authorisation</Name>
        <Description>Error caused by a received message that could not be processed further due to a missing authorization or approval for the prodecure. Leads to the rejection of the received message.</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>AE</Id>
        <Name>Authentication exception</Name>
        <Description>Error caused by a received message that could not be processed further due missing authentication or registration for the procedure. Leads to the rejection of the received message.</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>PT</Id>
        <Name>Process termination</Name>
        <Description>A query response of a Search Notice Request is cancelled or terminated. </Description>
    </Code>
</CodeList>
