<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<CodeList xmlns="urn:fdc:difi.no:2017:vefa:structure:CodeList-1" xmlns:gc="http://docs.oasis-open.org/codelist/ns/genericode/1.0/">
	<Title>Size Type Code (openPEPPOL)</Title>
	<Identifier>TRED8155</Identifier>
	<Version>3.0</Version>
	<Agency>openPEPPOL</Agency>
	<Code>
		<Id>1</Id>
		<Name>A tank coated with dime.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>2</Id>
		<Name>A tank coated with epoxy.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>6</Id>
		<Name>A tank capable of holding pressurized goods.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>7</Id>
		<Name>A tank capable of keeping goods refrigerated.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>9</Id>
		<Name>A tank made of stainless steel.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>10</Id>
		<Name>A 40 foot refrigerated container that is not actively controlling temperature of the product.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>12</Id>
		<Name>80 x 120 cm.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>13</Id>
		<Name>100 x 120 cm.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>14</Id>
		<Name>Non self-propelled vehicle designed for the carriage of cargo so that it can be towed by a motor vehicle.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>15</Id>
		<Name>A 20 foot refrigerated container that is not actively controlling temperature of the product.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>16</Id>
		<Name>Standard pallet exchangeable following international convention.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>17</Id>
		<Name>Non self propelled vehicle without front wheels designed for the carriage of cargo and provided with a kingpin.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>18</Id>
		<Name>A tank container with a length of 20 feet.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>19</Id>
		<Name>A tank container with a length of 30 feet.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>20</Id>
		<Name>A tank container with a length of 40 feet.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>21</Id>
		<Name>A container owned by InterContainer, a European railway subsidiary, with a length of 20 feet.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>22</Id>
		<Name>A container owned by InterContainer, a European railway subsidiary, with a length of 30 feet.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>23</Id>
		<Name>A container owned by InterContainer, a European railway subsidiary, with a length of 40 feet.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>24</Id>
		<Name>A refrigerated tank with a length of 20 feet.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>25</Id>
		<Name>A refrigerated tank with a length of 30 feet.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>26</Id>
		<Name>A refrigerated tank with a length of 40 feet.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>27</Id>
		<Name>A tank container owned by InterContainer, a European railway subsidiary, with a length of 20 feet.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>28</Id>
		<Name>A tank container owned by InterContainer, a European railway subsidiary, with a length of 30 feet.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>29</Id>
		<Name>A tank container, owned by InterContainer, a European railway subsidiary, with a length of 40 feet.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>30</Id>
		<Name>A refrigerated tank owned by InterContainer, a European railway subsidiary, with a length of 20 feet.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>31</Id>
		<Name>Temperature controlled container measuring 30 feet.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>32</Id>
		<Name>A refrigerated tank owned by InterContainer, a European railway subsidiary, with a length of 40 feet.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>33</Id>
		<Name>A movable case with a length less than 6,15 metres.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>34</Id>
		<Name>A movable case with a length between 6,15 metres and 7,82 metres.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>35</Id>
		<Name>A movable case with a length between 7,82 metres and 9,15 metres.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>36</Id>
		<Name>A movable case with a length between 9,15 metres and 10,90 metres.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>37</Id>
		<Name>A movable case with a length between 10,90 metres and 13,75 metres.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>38</Id>
		<Name>A steel open top unit of about 1,5 * 1,5 * 2,5 meters for road transport of bulk cargo.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>39</Id>
		<Name>Temperature controlled container measuring 20 feet.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>40</Id>
		<Name>A temperature controlled container measuring 40 feet.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>41</Id>
		<Name>A 30 foot refrigerated (reefer) container that is not actively cooling the product.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>42</Id>
		<Name>Two trailers linked together one behind another and pulled by one tractor.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>43</Id>
		<Name>An open top container that is 20 feet in internal length.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>44</Id>
		<Name>A closed top container that is 20 feet in internal length.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>45</Id>
		<Name>A closed top container that is 40 feet in internal length.</Name>
	</Code>
</CodeList>