<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<CodeList xmlns="urn:fdc:difi.no:2017:vefa:structure:CodeList-1" xmlns:gc="http://docs.oasis-open.org/codelist/ns/genericode/1.0/">
	<Title>Transport equipment type code (openPEPPOL) </Title>
    <Identifier>UNCL8053</Identifier>
    <Version>1.0</Version>
    <Agency>openPEPPOL</Agency>
	<Code>
		<Id>AA</Id>
		<Name>Ground equipment being fuelled or serviced.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>AB</Id>
		<Name>Chain used in the securing of cargo.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>AD</Id>
		<Name>Temperature recorder to provide a record of the actual temperature.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>AE</Id>
		<Name>The part of the vehicle where the cargo is loaded.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>AG</Id>
		<Name>A cardboard platform used for holding product for storage or transportation.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>AH</Id>
		<Name>A code to indicate that there is no special equipment needed.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>AI</Id>
		<Name>A compartment forming part of a transport vessel.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>AJ</Id>
		<Name>Type of open container used for carrying objects.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>AK</Id>
		<Name>To indicate that the equipment is an aircraft.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>AL</Id>
		<Name>A device used for medical purposes.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>AM</Id>
		<Name>A refrigerated (reefer) container that is actively cooling the product.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>AN</Id>
		<Name>A pallet with standard dimensions 80*120 centimetres made of synthetic material.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>AO</Id>
		<Name>A standard pallet with standard dimensions 100*120 centimetres made of synthetic material.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>AP</Id>
		<Name>Equipment used to store and transport clothing in a hanging position.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>AQ</Id>
		<Name>Trailer designated for combined road/rail use.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>AT</Id>
		<Name>Empty rail wagon added to the loaded wagons, when goods are longer than the loaded wagon.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>BL</Id>
		<Name>A piece of equipment that is normally a piece of wood to fix cargo (e.g. coils) during transport.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>BPN</Id>
		<Name>A box pallet which cannot be exchanged.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>BPO</Id>
		<Name>A road vehicle capable of carrying goods which is being carried on another means of transport.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>BPP</Id>
		<Name>A road vehicle capable of carrying goods with an attached trailer which is being carried on another means of transport.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>BPQ</Id>
		<Name>A trailer accompanied by a self-propelling tractor unit which is being carried on another means of transport.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>BPR</Id>
		<Name>Bag intended primarily for the conveyance of postal items.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>BPS</Id>
		<Name>Tray intended primarily for the conveyance of letter mail items of size slightly exceeding C5, in which the items are stood on their long edge.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>BPT</Id>
		<Name>Wheeled wire cage.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>BPU</Id>
		<Name>Tray intended primarily for the conveyance of letter mail items of from C5 up to in excess of C4, in which the items are stacked one on top of another. May also be used for letter mail smaller items stood on their long edge.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>BPV</Id>
		<Name>Postal item which is conveyed individually, with only the wrapping provided by the mailer for protection.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>BPW</Id>
		<Name>Device, consisting of a flat surface mounted on a wheels, which is designed for the conveyance of items which may safely be stacked. Normally also equipped with a handle to allow the device to be easily manoeuvred.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>BPX</Id>
		<Name>The container is not compliant with the Customs Convention on Containers.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>BPY</Id>
		<Name>A euro-pallet of type Y that may not be exchanged.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>BPZ</Id>
		<Name>80 X 60 cm pallet on casters.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>BR</Id>
		<Name>Flat bottomed inland cargo vessel for canals and rivers with or without own propulsion for the purpose of transported goods. (Synonym: Lighter).</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>BX</Id>
		<Name>An enclosed railway goods wagon.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>CH</Id>
		<Name>A wheeled carriage onto which an ocean container is mounted for inland conveyance.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>CN</Id>
		<Name>Equipment item as defined by ISO for transport. It must be of: A) permanent character, strong enough for repeated use; B) designed to facilitate the carriage of goods, by one or more modes of transport, without intermediate reloading; C) fitted with devices for its ready handling, particularly.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>DPA</Id>
		<Name>A set of panels fixed inside a porthole.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>DPB</Id>
		<Name>120 X 60 cm pallet on casters.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>EFP</Id>
		<Name>A flat euro-pallet that may be exchanged.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>EYP</Id>
		<Name>A euro-pallet of type Y that may be exchanged.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>FPN</Id>
		<Name>A flat euro-pallet that may not be exchanged.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>FPR</Id>
		<Name>A non-exchangeable flat pallet owned by a railroad.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>IL</Id>
		<Name>Lidded stackable rigid tray compliant with CEN TS 14482:2002.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>LAR</Id>
		<Name>A rope for lashing cargo.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>LU</Id>
		<Name>A mechanical device used in the loading and/or unloading of cargo into and from transport equipment.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>MPA</Id>
		<Name>A panel which can be moved.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>PA</Id>
		<Name>A platform on which goods can be stacked in order to facilitate the movement by a forklift or sling.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>PBP</Id>
		<Name>A box pallet identified as being privately owned.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>PFP</Id>
		<Name>A flat pallet identified as being privately owned.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>PL</Id>
		<Name>A piece of equipment normally having a flat surface, or prepared for carrying cargo with a specific shape.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>PPA</Id>
		<Name>A panel used for protection.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>PST</Id>
		<Name>A portable heating unit.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>RF</Id>
		<Name>A railway wagon without raised sides or ends.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>RG</Id>
		<Name>A generator used to control the temperature in temperature-controlled transport equipment.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>RGF</Id>
		<Name>Storage tank or facility capable of receiving shipment of goods or commodity.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>RO</Id>
		<Name>Rope used in the securing of cargo.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>RR</Id>
		<Name>To identify that the equipment is a rail car.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>SPP</Id>
		<Name>A pallet identified as special.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>STR</Id>
		<Name>A narrow strip of flexible material.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>SW</Id>
		<Name>Rectangular equipment unit without wheels, which can be mounted on a chassis or positioned on legs.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>TE</Id>
		<Name>A vehicle without motive power, designed for the carriage of cargo and to be towed by a motor vehicle.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>TP</Id>
		<Name>Waterproof material, e.g. canvas, to spread over cargo to protect it from getting wet.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>TS</Id>
		<Name>Identification of loading tackle used (sheets, ropes, chains, etc.), as specified in DCU 9 to CIM Article 13; and of containers, as specified in Articles 5 and 10 of Annex III to CIM (CIM 17).</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>TSU</Id>
		<Name>A device to support a tarpaulin.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>UL</Id>
		<Name>An aircraft container or pallet.</Name>
	</Code>
</CodeList>