<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<CodeList xmlns="urn:fdc:difi.no:2017:vefa:structure:CodeList-1">
	<Title>Transport Means Type Code</Title>
    <Identifier>UNECERec28</Identifier>
    <Version>1.0</Version>
    <Agency>UN/ECE</Agency>
	<Code>
		<Id>31</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed for hauling loads.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>32</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle with a tank.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>33</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle with an engine designed for pulling.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>34</Id>
		<Name>Closed automotive vehicle designed for carrying freight.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>35</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed with a tank lifting capability.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>36</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed for carrying dry bulk cargo.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>37</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed for carrying containers.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>38</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed for carrying motorcars.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>39</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed for the carriage of frozen cargo.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>60</Id>
		<Name>Multimodal transport of unknown type.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>70</Id>
		<Name>Fixed transport installation of unknown type.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>71</Id>
		<Name>A line of one or more pipes for continuous transport of liquid or gas commodity.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>72</Id>
		<Name>A line of one or more cables or wires for continuous transport of electricity.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>80</Id>
		<Name>Vessel of unknown type.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>81</Id>
		<Name>Motorized vessel designed for carrying general cargo.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>82</Id>
		<Name>Motorized vessel designed for carrying liquid cargo.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>83</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed for carrying containers.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>84</Id>
		<Name>Vessel with tanks designed for carrying gas.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>85</Id>
		<Name>Motorized vessel designed for carrying cargo and capable of towing.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>86</Id>
		<Name>Motorized vessel designed for carrying liquid cargo and capable of towing.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>87</Id>
		<Name>Motorized vessel designed for carrying general cargo that has one or more vessels alongside.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>88</Id>
		<Name>Motorized vessel designed for carrying general cargo alongside a vessel designed for carrying liquid cargo.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>89</Id>
		<Name>Motorized vessel designed for carrying general cargo, pushing one or more vessels also designed for carrying general cargo.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>150</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to carry general cargo.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>151</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to carry unit loads</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>152</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to carry bulk cargo.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>153</Id>
		<Name>Vessel solely equipped with tanks to carry cargo.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>154</Id>
		<Name>Tanker designed to carry liquefied gas.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>155</Id>
		<Name>Tanker designed to carry other special liquids.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>157</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to carry cargo and passengers.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>159</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to carry more than 12 passengers.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>160</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to give assistance.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>170</Id>
		<Name>Sea-going vessel, not otherwise specified.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>172</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to assist in work.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>173</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to push other vessels.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>174</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to scoop or suck mud or sand.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>175</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed for fishing.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>176</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed for research and education.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>177</Id>
		<Name>Vessel operated by a Navy.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>178</Id>
		<Name>Any floating structure.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>180</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed for recreation.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>181</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed for speed, often used for recreation.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>182</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed primarily for sailing outfitted with an auxiliary motor.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>183</Id>
		<Name>A specific type of vessel mostly used for pleasure and designed for sailing.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>184</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed for sport fishing.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>185</Id>
		<Name>Vessel longer than 20 metres, designed for recreation.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>189</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed for recreation, not otherwise specified.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>190</Id>
		<Name>Fast, all-purpose vessel.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>191</Id>
		<Name>Vessel with wing-like structure for skimming at high speed.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>192</Id>
		<Name>Fast vessel designed with two parallel hulls.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>210</Id>
		<Name>One or more rail wagons pulled or pushed by one or more locomotive units, or self-propelled, that move over rail tracks.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>220</Id>
		<Name>Train designed to carry passengers.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>230</Id>
		<Name>Train for carrying freight.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>310</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed for carrying mail.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>311</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed with a cargo-dumping capability.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>312</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed for lifting cargo and heavy objects.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>313</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed for shoveling sand and other bulk material.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>314</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed with a fixed platform.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>315</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed for lifting and transporting containers.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>320</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle with cargo crane.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>330</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed for carrying more than 8 passengers including the driver.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>341</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed for making fast deliveries.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>342</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed for light carriage.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>343</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed for carrying furniture.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>360</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed for towing one or more trailers.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>362</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed for carrying frozen goods with a trailer designed for carrying temperature-controlled goods.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>363</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle with trailer designed to carry temperature-controlled goods.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>364</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed for carrying refrigerated goods with a trailer designed for carrying temperature-controlled goods.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>365</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed for carrying frozen goods with a trailer designed for carrying refrigerated goods.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>366</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed to carry temperature-controlled goods with a trailer designed to carry refrigerated goods.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>367</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle with an opening floor with an extendable trailer.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>368</Id>
		<Name>Rigid automotive vehicle designed with a tank with a tank trailer.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>369</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed for bulk carrying with a tank trailer.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>370</Id>
		<Name>Rigid automotive vehicle designed with a tank with a trailer capable of carrying bulk cargo and liquid.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>371</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle and trailer both designed for carrying bulk cargo.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>372</Id>
		<Name>Automotive tautliner vehicle with extendable trailer.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>373</Id>
		<Name>Automotive tautliner vehicle with removable roof and extendable trailer.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>374</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed for carrying bulk cargo with an extendable trailer.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>375</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed for carrying refrigerated goods with a trailer designed for carrying frozen goods.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>376</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed for carrying temperature-controlled goods with a trailer designed for carrying frozen goods.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>377</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed for carrying furniture with a trailer.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>378</Id>
		<Name>Automotive tautliner vehicle with trailer designed for carrying furniture.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>379</Id>
		<Name>Automotive tautliner vehicle designed with a removable roof with a trailer designed for carrying furniture.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>380</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed with a tip-up capability with a gondola trailer.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>381</Id>
		<Name>Automotive tautliner vehicle with a gondola trailer.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>382</Id>
		<Name>Automotive tautliner vehicle with removable roof and a gondola trailer.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>383</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle with an opening floor and with a gondola trailer.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>384</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed for carrying bulk cargo with a gondola trailer.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>385</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed with a tip-up capability with an extendable gondola trailer.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>386</Id>
		<Name>Automotive tautliner vehicle with an extendable gondola trailer.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>387</Id>
		<Name>Automotive tautliner vehicle designed with a removable roof and with an extendable gondola trailer.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>388</Id>
		<Name>Automotive tautliner vehicle designed with an opening floor and with an extendable gondola trailer.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>389</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed for carrying bulk cargo with an extendable gondola trailer.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>390</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed with a tip-up capability with an opening-floor trailer.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>391</Id>
		<Name>Automotive tautliner vehicle with opening-floor trailer.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>392</Id>
		<Name>Automotive tautliner vehicle with a removable roof, with an opening-floor trailer.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>393</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle and trailer both with opening floors.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>394</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed for carrying bulk cargo with an opening-floor trailer.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>395</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed to pull a trailer, with a trailer attached.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>396</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle with a tilt capability with a trailer also with a tilt capability.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>397</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed to carry refrigerated goods with a trailer also capable of carrying refrigerated goods.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>398</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle capable of carrying frozen goods with a trailer also capable of carrying frozen goods.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>399</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed to carry household effects with a trailer also capable of carrying household effects.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>810</Id>
		<Name>Motorized vessel designed for carrying general cargo, pushing at least one vessel designed to carry liquid cargo.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>811</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to push or pull another vessel that is also capable of carrying general cargo.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>812</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to push or pull another vessel also capable of carrying liquid cargo.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>813</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to push or pull another vessel that is also capable of carrying general cargo tied to one or more other vessels.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>814</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to push or pull another vessel that is also capable of carrying either general or liquid cargo tied to one or more other vessels.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>815</Id>
		<Name>Lighter designed for carrying general cargo.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>816</Id>
		<Name>Lighter designed for carrying liquid cargo.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>817</Id>
		<Name>Lighter designed for carrying containers.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>818</Id>
		<Name>Lighter designed for carrying gas.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>821</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed for pushing/towing, facilitating the movement of one cargo barge.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>822</Id>
		<Name>Combination designed for pushing/towing, facilitating the movement of two cargo barges.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>823</Id>
		<Name>Combination designed for pushing/towing, facilitating the movement of three cargo barges.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>824</Id>
		<Name>Combination designed for pushing/towing, facilitating the movement of four cargo barges.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>825</Id>
		<Name>Combination designed for pushing/towing, facilitating the movement of five cargo barges.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>826</Id>
		<Name>Combination designed for pushing/towing, facilitating the movement of six cargo barges.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>827</Id>
		<Name>Combination designed for pushing/towing, facilitating the movement of seven cargo barges.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>828</Id>
		<Name>Combination designed for pushing/towing, facilitating the movement of eight cargo barges.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>829</Id>
		<Name>Combination designed for pushing/towing, facilitating the movement of nine or more cargo barges.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>831</Id>
		<Name>Combination designed for pushing/towing, moving one tanker or gas barge.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>832</Id>
		<Name>Combination designed for pushing/towing, moving two barges of which at least one tanker or gas barge.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>833</Id>
		<Name>Combination designed for pushing/towing, moving three barges of which at least one is a tanker or gas barge.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>834</Id>
		<Name>Combination designed for pushing/towing, moving four barges of which at least one is a tanker or gas barge.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>835</Id>
		<Name>Combination designed for pushing/towing, moving five barges of which at least one is a tanker of gas barge.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>836</Id>
		<Name>Combination designed for pushing/towing, moving six barges of which at least one is a tanker or gas barge.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>837</Id>
		<Name>Combination designed for pushing/towing, moving seven barges of which at least one is a tanker or gas barge.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>838</Id>
		<Name>Combination designed for pushing/towing, moving eight barges of which at least one is a tanker or gas barge.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>839</Id>
		<Name>Combination designed for pushing/towing, moving nine or more barges of which at least one is a tanker or gas barge.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>840</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed for pushing another vessel that is the only boat used for a tow.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>841</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed for pushing another vessel that is involved in one or more concurrent tows.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>842</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed for pushing another vessel that is assisting one vessel or a combination of vessels or tugs and vessels.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>843</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed for pushing.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>844</Id>
		<Name>Vessels designed for carrying passengers.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>845</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to perform a specific dedicated service.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>846</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to perform a specific type of work.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>847</Id>
		<Name>An object in tow that is not otherwise specified.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>848</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed for fishing.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>849</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed for carrying and delivering bunkers.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>850</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to carry liquid or bulk chemicals.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>851</Id>
		<Name>A floating object that is not otherwise specified.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>852</Id>
		<Name>A tender (vessel for logistical support), dealing with the transport of small material and maintenance requirements outside the port area on rivers and other inland waterways.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>853</Id>
		<Name>A vessel for the supervision by police of applicable rules and regulations.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>854</Id>
		<Name>A port tender (vessel for logistical support), dealing with the transport of material and people within a port area.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>855</Id>
		<Name>A vessel of the competent authority (waterway) dealing with the surveillance of navigation.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1501</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to carry grain.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1502</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to carry logs and timber.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1503</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to carry wood chips.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1504</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to carry steel products.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1505</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to carry general cargo and containers.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1506</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to carry temperature-controlled cargo.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1511</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to carry containers only.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1512</Id>
		<Name>Vessel with ramp designed to carry roll-on/roll-off cargo.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1513</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to carry automotive vehicles or their knock-down parts.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1514</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to carry livestock.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1515</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to carry barges. Lash means lighters aboard ship.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1516</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to carry chemicals in bulk or drums not in tanks.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1517</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to carry irradiated fuel.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1518</Id>
		<Name>Ship designed to carry heavy cargo.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1519</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to carry both containers and roll-on/roll-off cargo.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1521</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to carry dry bulk (expellers).</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1522</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to carry ore.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1523</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to carry cement.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1524</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to carry gravel.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1525</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to carry coal.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1531</Id>
		<Name>Tanker designed to carry crude oil.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1532</Id>
		<Name>Tanker designed to carry chemicals in coastal traffic.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1533</Id>
		<Name>Tanker designed to carry chemicals in deep sea.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1534</Id>
		<Name>Tanker designed to carry oil and other derivatives.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1541</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to carry Liquefied Petroleum Gas (LPG).</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1542</Id>
		<Name>Tanker designed to carry Liquefied Natural Gas (LNG).</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1543</Id>
		<Name>Tanker designed to carry Liquefied Natural Gas (LNG) and Liquefied Petroleum Gas (LPG).</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1551</Id>
		<Name>Tanker designed asphalt and bitumen.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1552</Id>
		<Name>Tanker designed to carry molasses.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1553</Id>
		<Name>Tanker designed to carry vegetable oil.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1591</Id>
		<Name>Passenger ship designed to carry tourists on specified routes.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1592</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to ply regularly between two or more ports.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1593</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to carry passengers, not otherwise specified.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1594</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to carry passengers and mainly propelled by sails.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1601</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to tow objects but sailing alone.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1602</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to tow, and towing an object.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1603</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to salvage.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1604</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to effect rescue operations.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1605</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to combat oil spills.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1606</Id>
		<Name>Object designed for drilling oil at sea.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1607</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to serve as a hospital at sea.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1711</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to convey pilots to/from ships.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1712</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to guard, patrol or measure.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1721</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to provide supplies.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1723</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to provide offshore support.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1724</Id>
		<Name>Flat-bottomed vessel with a flat deck.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1725</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to dump stones.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1726</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to lay cable.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1727</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to handle buoys.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1728</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to break ice.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1729</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to lay pipe.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1751</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed to drag a bag-like net.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1752</Id>
		<Name>Small vessel that sometimes can be carried on a larger ship.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1753</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed as a fish factory.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1761</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed for fishery research.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1762</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed for climate registration.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1763</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed for environmental monitoring and measurement.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1764</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed for scientific purposes.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1765</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed for training, powered by sail.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1766</Id>
		<Name>Vessel designed for training.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1781</Id>
		<Name>A crane mounted on a barge or pontoon.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>1782</Id>
		<Name>A submersible floating structure used as a dock.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>2201</Id>
		<Name>Train designed for high speed.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>2202</Id>
		<Name>Passenger train that includes carriages for sleeping.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>2203</Id>
		<Name>A chartered train.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>2301</Id>
		<Name>Train for carrying freight to the same destination.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>2302</Id>
		<Name>Train for carrying containers.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>2303</Id>
		<Name>Train with a single wagon for carrying freight.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>2304</Id>
		<Name>Train with more than one and less than 20 wagons for carrying freight.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>2305</Id>
		<Name>Train with more than 20 wagons for carrying freight.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3100</Id>
		<Name>Automotive tautline truck with trailer capable of carrying household effects.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3101</Id>
		<Name>Automotive tautline vehicle with removable roof and a trailer capable of carrying household effects.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3102</Id>
		<Name>Automobile towing a house trailer.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3103</Id>
		<Name>Automotive tautline vehicle with a 25 tonne capacity.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3104</Id>
		<Name>Automotive tautline vehicle with a 25 tonne capacity and a removable roof.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3105</Id>
		<Name>Articulated automotive vehicle with a flat bed and 25 tonne capacity.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3106</Id>
		<Name>Articulated automotive vehicle with a flat bed and 25 tonne capacity with a 10 metre crane attached.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3107</Id>
		<Name>Articulated automotive vehicle with a flat bed and 25 tonne capacity with a 15 metre crane attached.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3108</Id>
		<Name>Articulated automotive vehicle with a flat bed and 25 tonne capacity with an 18 metre crane attached.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3109</Id>
		<Name>Articulated automotive vehicle with a flat bed and 10 tonne capacity.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3110</Id>
		<Name>Automotive tautline vehicle with a 25 tonne capacity and a 90 cubic metre trailer.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3111</Id>
		<Name>Automotive tautline vehicle with a 25 tonne capacity and a 120 cubic metre trailer.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3112</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle with flat bed and trailer and 10 metre crane.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3113</Id>
		<Name>Articulated automotive vehicle with tank designed for carrying liquid or bulk goods.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3114</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle with flat bed and a 15 tonne capacity.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3115</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle with flat bed and a 15 tonne capacity and attached crane.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3116</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed to carry temperature-controlled goods.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3117</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed to carry refrigerated goods.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3118</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed to carry frozen goods.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3119</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed to carry temperature-controlled goods.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3120</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed to carry refrigerated goods.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3121</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed to carry bulk goods.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3122</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed with a tip-up capability.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3123</Id>
		<Name>Articulated automotive vehicle designed with a tip-up capability.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3124</Id>
		<Name>Rigid automotive vehicle designed with a tank.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3125</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle with non-rigid sides.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3126</Id>
		<Name>Automotive tautline vehicle with a removable roof.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3127</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle with a floor that can be opened.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3128</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed to carry frozen goods.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3129</Id>
		<Name>A truck with a crane for moving goods, without a trailer.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3130</Id>
		<Name>A truck with a crane for moving goods, with a trailer.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3131</Id>
		<Name>A truck with a crane for lifting goods, without a trailer.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3132</Id>
		<Name>A truck with a crane for lifting goods, with a trailer.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3133</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle licensed to ply for hire.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3134</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed for carrying furniture.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3135</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed for the delivery of fuel from a fixed installation to a means of transport.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3136</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed to carry a small number of passengers.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3137</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle with a hydraulic lifting device on the rear of the vehicle for loading and unloading goods.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3138</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed with fortified body for enhanced protection.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3201</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle with raisable work platform.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3301</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle with an attached trailer for carrying passengers and/or luggage.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3302</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed for highway travel.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3303</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed for sightseeing.</Name>
	</Code>
	<Code>
		<Id>3304</Id>
		<Name>Automotive vehicle designed to carry passengers and their baggage between an airport and a city and return.</Name>
	</Code>
</CodeList>
